Hi everyone and welcome to a new video. I'm going to show you some party outfits today and
I introduced neoprene as a material a few videos ago. I have more neoprene to show you today and
to talk a bit more about it but also something like this. So it's going to be fun and all these
outfits are from a Dutch shop called Moonheels but I'll just start right away with the first outfit.
This was one of my favorite designs when I saw it and I'm going to start with this one.
Okay, shoes next.
Alright, outfit complete. Now I'm going to have a look in the mirror because I didn't try it before.
Oh, I like it.
There is a ruffle party in the back that makes the booty look really nice.
Overall I think I have to wear a different bra with the straps here or pasties or whatever.
But I totally like the design.
It's so cool.
I mean I would wear this to a goth party but also to a cocktail party.
It's like a hybrid dress.
And it also looks super elegant.
I can imagine that it also looks good with some boots or all-money boots.
Of course wearing tights is a bit more complicated because it's completely see-through.
So yeah, I went with the plain black Dessus and I think it doesn't disrupt the pattern
of the dress too much so I'm fine with it.
I really like it.
So if I would wear the dress to a photoshoot and would have the straps problem I would
simply do it like this and push the straps in the bra.
Tada!
Kinda have the urge to wear this one out.
But I think I'll switch on to the next outfit and go into the neoprene ensemble here.
So this is a mini skirt and a top.
Of course you can combine the top with normal pants or leggings.
Would also be a nice look.
But I think this is a cool combination.
These Fashion Neoprene items are 0.9 mm thick so your normal diving suit is thicker than that
and they have a polyamide layer on the inside so you can dress it really fast and you do not have the same problems you have with latex
and also do not shine it like you would do with latex.
So it has this matte look and feeling and it's supposed to stay matte.
So different look here.
Also take care with fingernails and sharp objects because you can damage the material.
And what I particularly like about it is the figure shaping effect.
I think it makes a great shape of the body.
Alright, I have a second new green outfit for later.
but first I'm...
First I'm going to show you this dress, also a black little dress and I'm really curious how this is going to look.
Third outfit, a cocktail dress and I really wish it was summer and I could wear these outside.
This one is cool as well. I think it's more like a bluish black and the fabric is called
Dvoré. I don't know how to pronounce it to be honest because there's an accent. Also
known as burnt out velvet fabrics. So it's really soft and feels velvety but it's also
slightly see-through and the glue is in the back.
So I think it looks super cool. Of course you can't wear a bra but in
summer it's going to be totally fine.
I totally like this look.
It's also very comfortable and I love the cut here and the neck.
I don't think it's a neck holder cut but I'm not sure.
Anyway let's switch into the next neoprene dress.
Same boots, different dress.
It's a similar cut to the one before that but made of neoprene again and it's super easy to get inside. I really love the fact about it because it's tight but still easy to dress.
And what I noticed the longer you wear it the more the fabric attunes to your body shape and it's like a memory form so it's really comfortable as well.
and also there is a small ring here.
So all outfits are provided to me by moonheels.nl.
It is an online shop from the Netherlands.
The specialty is that they also have a showroom in the Netherlands.
So if you are from the Netherlands, check out the online shop and then you can actually
try your selection on there which is really cool.
And they have a lot of designs, over a thousand designs.
These neoprene fashion but also all the other party and clubwear outfits I showed you plus
a lot more.
Their fashion is dress code approved by a lot of the big Dutch fetish parties.
So if you don't know what you wear to a party you can definitely find something at the Moonheels
shop.
And I do like that they do not only offer the dresses and the outfits but also everything you need to complement your outfit like ties, lingerie, stuff like that. Just check it out. I'll link it down below.
The package I received from Moonheels was kind of a surprise package because I did find two other dresses in there.
These pink dresses, I think they're totally fun. I'm going to try them on for you guys.
guys if you're into I don't know not gothic parties you may like them okay I don't know
um I found matching shoes so that's definitely plus point and of course my hair does match
um other than that I'm really not used to this color
combination here. Wow it's bright. So if you're into rave parties I think this is your outfit.
Again I like the cut. And oh there's a bit of sparkle going on. A bit of glitter. I think
it's a cute dress normally not what I wear though there's second one completely pink I'm going to
try this on because I want to see how it looks it's pink it's way too bright for me oh my gosh
I have no idea when I ever wore something like this. I don't know maybe you could like kink it
up with some latex stockings gloves and a latex corset on top of it. I don't know.
Definitely not my color but it's fun and it's super comfortable and also kind of looks nice.
Ah, damn it, this hair. Everything looks good with the hair.
No, just kidding.
I think it's enough for today, especially with the last two dresses.
My top outfit today was the neoprene two-piece set with the top and the skirt,
followed by the first dress.
Yeah, I think these two were my favorites.
and I will do another neoprene video soon with more details and more information
and if you have any questions leave a comment down below also tell me what you
think of this dress and the one before that if it was too much yeah so have a
nice day see you around bye